Over the last 10 years, as the feckless, spineless, loser, failure Democrats have sold out their
constituencies time and time again, oftentimes you'll hear them making excuses such as,
but Trump, we're not in the majority, but we don't have any leverage.
And they make these excuses because Democrats love nothing more than surrendering.
They love capitulating and being complicit with the Republicans.
And for the last 10 years, Democratic and liberal voters have been accepting their fucking endless
excuses. And I'm wondering, are you guys finally there yet? Like this, this question's for the norm
libs. I mean, rank and file liberal democratic voters. Those of you who are usually the first
to race up to the front right after the Democrats gave up their leverage and sold you out to go,
what were they supposed to do? Are you guys there yet? Are you tired yet? Are you tired of being
gaslit, thrown under the bus, fucked over, sold out? Also that this pterodactyl and his corrupt,
incompetent fucking colleagues can look you in the face and lie to you and tell you to get over it
and that they tried. So everybody knows these were the Democrats that voted to reopen the government
and fuck you over. This is going to help the Republicans double your healthcare costs. Cause
you know what they got? You know what the Democrats got? Nothing. They got nothing. And you know what?
Let me correct that. When I say they didn't get anything, I mean, they didn't get anything for
the American people. They didn't get anything for you. They did get something for themselves.
I'll tell you at the end of the video, why they voted to reopen it and what they got.
Chuck Schumer did this on purpose. None of these people are up for reelection in 2026.
They think you're dumb because this is the Joe Manchin, Kyrsten Sinema playbook.
They want to fuck you over on a certain policy or they want to sell you out on something.
And so they find the lawmakers that are the least vulnerable in that moment. Kyrsten Sinema and
Joe Manchin when they knew they weren't going to run for reelection and people already hated
them. Now these are the boogeyman of the day. But don't let the point escape you.
This is on Chuck Schumer and their so-called leadership, because if it wasn't them, it
would be a new group. It's a revolving door of sellout, corrupt, weak fucks. This is just
this year's crop. Angus King is an independent. They know John Fetterman will never win reelection.
Gene Shaheen is retiring and the others aren't up for reelection until 2028, long enough for
you to forget. Do you see how this game is played? This motherfucker really put out that
statement after he had already caved going, I voted no. And I'm going to keep, you voted
no. Who gives a shit? You're the leader of the Senate. See, because these people think
you're stupid and they have no respect for you. They think you're not going to notice
that even though he's going, well, I voted no. So don't get mad at me. The reason why they
even had that vote is because he allowed it. He is the Senate leader. He is the one
that could have kept his caucus in line the same way that Mitch McConnell always kept his
caucus in line. But did he? No, of course he did not. And do you think any of these people
voted without his consent? Of course not. He then had the actual nerve to go on the Senate
floor and go, no matter how this vote turns out, we're going to continue to fight. That was
the fight. Democrats love to do this gaslighting thing where they talk about how they're going
to keep fighting for you as they're surrendering. So as he is surrendering to the Republicans,
as they are selling you out and throwing you under the bus, they'll look you straight in
the face and go, we're going to keep fighting for you. No, literally. Here's Cortez Maso doing
that same exact thing. This is where the fight really begins. It's just the beginning. No,
no. That was the fight. The fight was happening just then and you guys caved. But again, they
gaslight you and go, oh, hi guys. As we're caving, as we're selling you out, we're going
to explain our selling out to you by telling you that we're still fighting for you as we
already gave up the fight. This is a disaster. This is a disaster. They caved getting nothing.
Nothing. They got, maybe, maybe we'll talk about it. All right. So now to the why, which I said
I would explain. It is because Trump was threatening to get the Republicans to nuke
the filibuster. The Republicans do not want to get rid of the filibuster. They don't want to get
rid of it because they don't want popular policy that would actually help the American people to be
able to pass. And it's for that reason that the Democrats also want to keep the filibuster.
Remember guys, the filibuster was the very convenient excuse that the Biden administration
used time and time again to not fulfill campaign promises. We can't do voting rights for you
guys. Like we promised the filibuster. We can't give you a $15 minimum wage. The filibuster. We
can't do anything about your healthcare. The filibuster. Taxing the rich, climate action,
gun safety law. Sorry, the filibuster. Looks like the Republicans are going to get their way again.
Republicans love the filibuster because it blocks any popular legislation from happening. And for the
things that the Republicans like to do with government, they don't need it. Because think about
the only things the Republicans care about doing. Right-wing judges and tax cuts for the rich and
deregulation. All of which can be done through budget reconciliation and through the executive
brand. So they love the filibuster because it serves as kind of a procedural cock block to doing
anything for the American people. They've admitted as much. They're like, oh, we're going to get a DC
statehood if we get rid of it. A base? That's why they don't want it. The Democrats, you would think,
would ostensibly want to get rid of the filibuster because they supposedly want to pass a lot of bills to
help the American people. And if you watch the election play out between Zoramandani and the corporate
establishment of the Democratic Party, you'll know the answer. It's because they're full of shit.
They don't actually give a fuck about you. They don't actually give a fuck about passing any of
the bills they promised they want to. So they finally decided that they were going to cave once
Trump threatened to get rid of the filibuster because they have a vested interest in protecting
the status quo just as much as the Republicans. They don't really care or want any of the things that
would help you to pass and neither do their donors. That is why they rush to sell you out even when
Democratic voters are telling them hold the line. And they did hold the line. Just not for you
because that's not who they're looking out for.